ふうう…
あっ…
ふわあ～ お腹ペコペコだよ
I'm so hungry...
コミマって明日も…
明日も 行くんだな
You're going to—
Comima again, right?
えっ？
うん
Yeah.
帰りは このくらいか？
多分
Will you be back around now?
I think so.
そうだ 紅莉栖ちゃんも行く？
I know! Kurisu-chan, you come, too!
人が多い所は 苦手だから
I'm not good with crowded places.
２日目は
そんなに 多くないと思うよ
It shouldn't be that crowded on the second day.
ねっ オカリンも 一緒に…
You should come, too, Okarin...
あ…
岡部 ちょっと
Okabe, come with me!
なんなのよ 帰ってから
ずっと ムスっとしちゃって
What's with you?
Ever since you got back, you've been down.
まゆりが 気を遣って
話しかけてんのが 分かんないの？
Can't you tell Mayuri is trying to cheer you up?
分かってる
でも 落ち着いていられるか
I know.
But...
I can't stay calm!
うん？
明日だぞ
Tomorrow is the day!
今日は無事でも 明日…
Even if she's safe today, tomorrow...
あっ…
はあ…
ああ…
何度目だ？ お前に こうやって…
How many times have I talked to you about this?
岡部？
Okabe?
聞いてほしいことがある
There's something I want to tell you.
Endless Apoptosis
まゆりが… 明日!?
Mayuri is going to die tomorrow?!
恐らく 死ぬ
I think so, yes.
始めは 13日の夜だった
At first, it was the night of the 13th.
それが
Ｄメールを １つ 取り消す度に
Each time I undo a D-mail, it goes back a day.
１日ずつ延びていって
俺は 明日 コミマについていく
I'll have to go with her to Comima tomorrow.
助ける手段があるの？
Do you have a way to save her?
まゆりの その時を 見届ける
そんなっ…
I'm going to wait for her to die.
You can't...
この世界線での
正確な デッドラインを
I need to know the precise deadline
in this world line.
知っておきたいんだ
その上で
Then I can time leap back again.
もう一度 タイムリープして…
え？
他に 手はない
There's no other way.
次に 取り消すのは
The next one to undo
桐生萌郁っていう人の
メールだったわよね
is that Kiryuu Moeka person's, right?
そうだ 内容も分かってる
That's right.
I know what she sent.
過去の自分に
携帯の機種変を やめさせたんだ
She sent a message
telling herself not to buy a new cell phone.
今回は
あいつの携帯から 送らないと…
This time, I need to send it from her phone.
岡部は その人を捜して
えっ？
You go find her...
ふう…
コミマには あたしが ついていく
お前…
I'll go with Mayuri to Comima.
You'll...
うまくいけば まゆりの…
If all goes well,
そうなる前に 何とかなるかも
I can protect Mayuri before she...
Do you know what you're saying?
分かってるのか？ もし
萌郁を 見つけられなかったら
If I can't find Moeka, you'll...
その時は…
すぐに連絡する
I'll contact you right away.
えっ…
And you can tell me anything, all right?
それから
何でも 話してくれていいから
どんなことでも
いつでも あたしに 相談して
No matter what,
no matter when, come talk to me.
ああ お前は 今までも…
Yeah. You're still...
忘れないで
Don't forget.
あなたは
どの世界線にいても 独りじゃない
No matter what world line you're in,
you aren't alone.
あたしがいる
I'm here!
Assistant
あっ
From: Assistant
Subject: Now in Ariake
"I'm in Ariake now.
Too many people here...
More than I expected.
Save me!"
フッ
｢萌郁から 返信はないが
バイト先を見つけた｣
"No response from Moeka, but I found her workplace."
｢そっちを調べてみる｣
"I'll check it out."
"Got it.
Don't force yourself."
うん
桐生萌郁？ ああ～
Kiryuu Moeka?
Oh, yeah. That chick who worked here
two or three days and quit. That was her name.
前に ２～３日来て
辞めたバイトが
そんな名前だったっけ
住所？ 分かるけど… 君 何？
Her address?
Yeah, I have it. But who are you?
えっ…
Heights White
Heights White 202
Kiryuu Moeka
はっ…
了解
あの…
Roger.
Hey...
うん？
桐生萌郁が… 自殺？
Kiryuu Moeka...
She killed herself?
間違えないんですか？
ああ
You're sure?
Yes.
いつです？
昨日の夜
When?
Last night.
ご遺体は
千代田第三病院に 運ばれている
The body was taken to Chiyoda Hospital 3.
身寄りが
誰も いないみたいでね…
She doesn't seem to have any relatives.
そんな…
No way...
あっ
はあ…
君 大丈夫か？
Are you all right?
Suicide?
自殺… なんで？
Why?
はあ…
仲間に殺された？
Did her companions kill her?
まゆりを殺す前に
Before she could kill Mayuri?
でも…
But...
理由なんて どうでもいい！
The reason doesn't matter!
このままじゃ まゆりが…
At this rate, Mayuri will...
はっ… タイムリープ
A time leap...
I need to time leap to before Moeka dies!
萌郁が死ぬ前に
タイムリープして…
はっ
はああ…
お 岡…
もしもし
Hello?
Oka... Okabe!
岡部 うっ… 死… まゆり…
She's...
Mayuri... Mayuri...
まゆりが ううっ…
デッドラインは 19時52分
The deadline is 19:52.
すまなかった
I'm sorry.
ああ！ 岡部
これ食べちゃったの？
Okabe!
Did you eat this?
ここ見なさいよ！
Look at the label!
It says "Makise" right here!
ちゃんと書いてあるでしょ
｢牧瀬｣って！
ちょっと 聞いてるの？
Are you listening?
Don't forget.
忘れないで
あなたは 独りじゃない
You aren't alone.
そうだ… そうだったな 紅莉栖
That's right.
You're right, Kurisu.
えっ あんた… 今 何て？
What did you just say...
Do you know a girl named Kiryuu Moeka?
桐生萌郁という女を
知っているか？
えっ 誰？
Who's that?
俺は タイムリープしてきた
I just did a time leap.
えっ？
What do you mean?
どういうこと？
Heights White
うっ…
あっ…
ＦＢ
FB...
ＦＢ ＦＢ…
答えて お願い…
Answer me...
Please...
ＦＢ
FB...
なんで…
なんで メール くれないの？
Why?
Why won't you message me?
お願い 返事を頂戴…
Please! Answer me!
ＦＢ
FB....
桐生萌郁
Kiryuu Moeka...
言われたとおりにやったのに
I did what you wanted... Why?
なんで…
俺だ 岡部だ
It's me, Okabe!
命令 頂戴 ＦＢ！
くっ…
Give me your orders, FB!
聞こえないのか？ おい！
Can't you hear me?!
ＦＢ ＦＢ
FB...
ＦＢ ＦＢ…
ちっ
FB...
うっ ううっ！ ふう…
えっ ああ… ああっ！
ふっ うう！ ううっ…
あっ あっ… いやっ いやあ…
N-No. No... No! Stop it!
いや！ やっ 返してよ うっ…
ふっ ううっ ふっうう…
うう うう… ううっ…
うう～ はっ はあっ うっ…
うっ！
うう…
うう うう！ ううっ！ うう！
ああ！ うう ううう…
うっ うう… ううっ はあ…
うう～ はあ はあ…
くうっ！ はっ はっ はっ…
ああ～ ううう～
ううう…
I'll never forgive her!
許さない
俺が あいつを
はあ～！
ふっ… ううっ！
あっ！
はあ はあ はあ…
うっ！ はっ はっ はっ…
か 返せ！
あっ はあ はあ…
G-Give it back.
うっ…
返せ 返せ！
Give it back!
Give it back now!
うう～ 返してよ～！
Give it back!
Okabe Rintarou
牧瀬 携帯は？
This is Makise.
Did you get the phone?
奪い取った
Ｄメールの設定を頼む
I stole it.
Prepare the D-mail!
It's ready.
出来てる… って 何の音？
Give it back!
What's that sound?
気にするな！
それより まゆりは？
Don't worry about it.
More importantly, what about Mayuri?
She's in Braun's TV Workshop.
ブラウン管工房 42型を点灯中よ
The 42" is on.
よし
紅莉栖！
あっ…
Kurisu! Activate it!
Change your phone. It will sell out soon,
and you won't be able to get one.
起動してくれ！
分かった
Right!
返せ 返せ…
Give it back!
これで 最後だ
This is the end...
If I send this, Mayuri will...
こいつを送れば まゆりは…
あっ
くうっ！
Give it back! Give it back!
返せ 返せ！
はっ…
携帯 返して！
Give me back my phone!
What?
何だ 何も起こらない どうだ？
Nothing happened.
What's going on there?
送ったの？
送った ちゃんと 作動したのか？
Did you send it!
I did!
Is it working?
放電現象は起こった どうしたの？
I saw the electricity.
What happened?
The Reading Steiner didn't activate!
運命探知が発動しない
えっ？
運命探知が発動しない なぜだ？
The Reading Steiner didn't activate...
Why?
うっ ううっ…
くっ…
返せ 返して！
Give it back! Give it back!
ちょっと 何なの？
Hey, what's going on?
うっ…
くっ…
返せ… 返せ 返せ！
Give it back! Give it back! Give it back!
ちっ やっぱりダメだ
It isn't working!
The D-mail works differently,
depending on who it was sent to.
Ｄメールは
受け取った相手しだいで
効果が左右される
岡部の文章じゃ
Does this mean your message
won't change her actions?
桐生萌郁の行動は
変えられないってこと？
えっ じゃあ どうすれば…
Then what do I do?
あっ
あっ… ああっ！
変わってない
It didn't change...
あいつ
機種変なんかしてなかったんだ
She didn't change her cell phone!
どういうこと？
ちゃんと確認したんでしょ？
What do you mean?
You confirmed it, right?
４日前に
携帯の 機種変更したけど
I changed my cell phone four days ago,
and I want to tell myself not to do it.
変えない方が 良かったって
自分に伝えたい
直前に
別のメールを打って 送ったんだ
She sent another just after that!
But that means we don't know
what was in that D-mail!
そんな！ Ｄメールの内容は
分からないってこと？
着信履歴が残っているはずだ
It should be in her outbox!
今 調べて… あっ
I'll look...
あっ…
返せ… 返せ！
うっ はっ…
Give it back!
ううっ…
どうしたの？ 岡部
What's wrong, Okabe?
Okabe?
岡部！
I'll have to call you back!
かけ直す
Give it back!
返せ 返せ…
うっ…
Give it back!
返せ！
うっ ううっ…
返せ 返せ！
Give it back!
Hey! What are you doing over there?
ちょっと 何やってんの！
返せ…
岡部～！
Okabe!
うわあ～！
ああ～！
ううっ…
ううっ！ くうっ うう…
あっ！ あっ…
返せ 返せ！
Give it back! Give it back!
くっ ふっ！
ううっ…
ううっ くう ふう うう…
ううっ 返せ…
うっ うう…
うっ ああ！
うっ うっ…
ふっ！ はあ はあ…
うっ！ はあ はあ はあ…
うう うう～！
あっ ああっ…
はっ！
まったく 何してんだか…
Jeez, what are they doing...
はっ あっ あっ…
はっ！ あっ…
Hey...
ちょっ…
Jeez! Couples these days...
ったく 最近のカップルときたら
おお 怖い 怖い
Scary.
はあ…
ふっ！ うう… はあっ はっ…
はあっ はあっ はあっ
はあっ はあっ…
はあ はあ…
What can I do?
どうしたら…
はっ
What can I do to make you give it back...
どうしたら… 返してくれる？
Do you remember sending a D-Mail?
Ｄメールを送ったことを
覚えているか？
ディ Ｄ… 何？
A D... What?
Two weeks ago,
２週間前 奇妙なメールを
受け取ったはずだ
you should have received a strange message
from your future self.
未来の自分から
どうして？
Why?
Tell me what it said! And I'll give it back.
内容を教えろ
そうしたら 返してやる
うっ…
どうした 言えないのか？
What's wrong? Can't you tell me?
うっ…
IBN5100に
ラウンダーに関係することか？
Does it have something to do with the IBN 5100?
With the Rounders?
はっ！
図星か？
Am I right?!
Tell me! What did it say?
答えろ メールの内容は？
くっ ううっ…
Don't you want your cell phone back?
携帯を返してほしくないのか？
I can't betray them.
裏切れない…
誰を？
Who?
That FB person?
ＦＢってヤツか？
あたしの指示は ＦＢから来る
I get my orders from FB.
ＦＢは あたしの全て
FB is everything to me...
So that's your leader?
そいつが お前たちの指揮官か？
うっ…
You can't betray FB?
裏切れないか
結構な 忠誠心じゃないか
It's great that you're so loyal.
But you know...
だがな そのＦＢとやらは
お前のことなんか
They don't give a damn about
what happens to you.
どうでもいいらしい
えっ…
They'll abandon you.
お前は このまま
ＦＢに捨てられるんだ
That's impossible...
そんなこと… ない
連絡がないんだろう？
They haven't contacted you, right?
お前は 裏切られたんだ
切り捨てられたんだよ！
You've been betrayed. Cut off!
違う！
ＦＢは そんな人じゃない
No!
FB isn't like that!
ＦＢは 私を助けてくれた
FB saved me...
...in Cabinet Office...
You've been used!
お前は 利用されたんだ
Rounder Recruitment
Do you know why you can tell me these things?
なんで
俺に そんなことが言えるか
分かるか？
FB is like a mother...
ＦＢは お母さんみたいな人
Subject: A Question
"What kind of job is it?"
Subject: Re: A Question
I have a type of time machine.
俺は 一種のタイムマシンを
持っている
The message from the future is proof.
未来から来たメールが 証拠だ
Subject: Another Question
"Can I do it, too?"
Subject: Re: Another Question
Of course. We offer everyone
the job that best suits them.
私を 必要としてくれた
They needed me...
"I've never worked before.
｢働いたこと ありません
I have no skills or things I'm good at."
特技も 何もありません｣
It's okay.
Let's do our best together.
ああっ…
And I've seen it!
その俺が 見てきたんだよ
You...
お前は
お前は…
くっ うう…
４日後
お前は この部屋で 自殺する
You will kill yourself in this room,
four days from now.
えっ？
You'll die here, alone,
still waiting to hear from FB!
ＦＢからの連絡を待ったまま
独り 孤独に ここで死ぬんだ
Lies.
ウソ…
本当だ
It's true.
もう ＦＢから
連絡なんて来やしない
You'll never hear from FB again.
捨てられたんだよ お前は
You've been abandoned.
You're lying.
ウソ…
いつから 返事が来ていない え？
How long has it been?
Well?
ずっと 待ち続けだろう
You've been waiting a while, right?
おかしいとは思わないか？
Don't you think that's strange?
うっ はああっ うっ…
You're going to die. Right here.
お前は死ぬんだ
ここで
嫌…
No...
In this dark, empty room...
この 薄暗い 空っぽの部屋で！
嫌…
No!
You killed Mayuri. And now you'll die!
まゆりを殺した お前は
ここで
独りで捨てられて 裏切られて
Alone, betrayed, like a piece of garbage!
ゴミクズみたいに 命を絶つんだ
嫌…
No!
You're going to kill yourself.
誰も お前を助けになんか来ない！
ＦＢもだ
No one's coming to save you!
Not even FB!
嫌～！
はあっ はあっ…
はあ… はあ…
うう～！
うう… 嫌～
ううっ…
うう～…
うう…
ううっ…
あっ
うう…
Sorry.
悪かった
You said they were like a mother.
｢母親｣って言ってたな
ＦＢってのは 女なのか？
Is FB a woman?
I think so.
多分…
あっ… ｢多分｣？
You think?
We've never met...
会ったことない
会いたくない
I don't want to meet them.
If I did, they'd hate me...
会えばきっと 幻滅させる
ああっ… その様子じゃ
電話も したことないか
From the look of it, I bet you've never
spoken by phone, either.
I'm amazed you did anything they ordered!
よく そんなヤツの言いなりに
居場所をくれた
They gave me a place...
あたし…
｢居場所｣？
A place?
くっ ううっ…
You're a fool.
バカだ お前は
うっ うう…
あっ
The retro-PC is in Yanabayashi Shrine.
Recover it immediately.
Okabe?
岡部？
はあ… ううっ 心配させんな！
Don't worry me!
You worried about me?
心配してくれたのか？
あっ ああ…
心配なんかしてない
I didn't!
I'm sorry.
すまない
それで？
So?
Then the one who stole the IBN 5100...
じゃあ
IBN5100を 盗み出したのは…
It was Moeka.
萌郁だ
今 どこにあるの？
Where is she now?
Don't ask any more.
それ以上は 何も
予定どおり Ｄメールを取り消す
I'll undo the D-mail, as planned.
July 31st, around 11:00 AM, right?
７月31日の午前11時ごろね
Don't go to the shrine.
It's a trap. It isn't there!
It's on!
起動した
ふう… 今度こそ
This time...
なっ… おおっ
はっ！
Why?
なぜだ？
どう？
Well?
It didn't work!
ダメだ
過去の桐生萌郁が
Ｄメールを 信じなかったのか
The Kiryuu Moeka from the past
didn't believe the D-mail?
She believed the first one, just in case?
念のため
初めのＤメールに 従ったのか
You could try another message!
別の文面で もう一度
あっ…
いや
No...
I think there's only one person she'll follow.
恐らく
萌郁を動かせるのは あいつだけだ
If I send a message from that phone, she'll obey it,
あいつの携帯から
メールを送ることができれば
no matter what it is!
無条件で従うはず
Who is it?
｢あいつ｣って？
うっ…
I'm going to look for FB.
俺はＦＢを捜す
If you have any clues...
何か 居場所に 心当たりは？
Even if she does, she won't tell me.
あっても 話すわけないか
What you were saying...
さっき言ってた
私が 誰かを殺したって
That I killed someone. Is that in the future?
未来のこと？
Yeah.
ああ
ＦＢの命令なら やるんだろう？
You'd do it if FB ordered you to, right?
I would. Absolutely.
やる きっと
利用されてると分かってもか？
Even if you knew you were being used?
そうやって 依存したまま
You're going to die...
Abandoned, still longing...
捨てられて 死んでいくんだ！
Four days. August 15th.
４日後 ８月15日
The world itself has decided that you will die.
お前の死は
この世界によって 決められている
There's no avoiding it.
避けられやしない
But I won't let it happen.
だが… 俺は そんなの ごめんだ
あっ…
I'll fight the world!
俺は 世界に あらがう！
はっ…
I will save Mayuri!
まゆりを 必ず救ってみせる
あ…
The coin locker...
コインロッカー…
あっ
In front of the Daibiru.
大ビル前…
IBN5100
The IBN 5100...
なっ！
そうやって 依存したまま
捨てられて 死んでいくんだ！
４日後 ８月15日
お前の死は
この世界によって 決められている
避けられやしない
だが… 俺は そんなの ごめんだ
あっ…
俺は 世界に あらがう！
はっ…